<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on chantal website</title>
    <link>http://redclould.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on chantal website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://redclould.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NTHU Presidential Hsing Chien Award</title>
      <link>http://redclould.github.io/posts/nthuaward/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://redclould.github.io/posts/nthuaward/</guid>
      <description>Introduction    Presidential Hsing Chien Award is presented by National Tsing Hua University to recognize student outstanding achievements in extracurricular activities.
Certificate     Recommendation Letter     Link    http://dsa.site.nthu.edu.tw/p/404-1266-196514.php?Lang=zh-tw</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 6th World Students Pair Go Championship – Runner-up</title>
      <link>http://redclould.github.io/posts/hugo-coder-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://redclould.github.io/posts/hugo-coder-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Official Website    http://www.pairgo.or.jp/amateur/30th/worldstudents/index_e.php
Introduction    The 6th World Students Pair Go Championship were hold in Tokyo, from 8 to 9 December 2019. We believe that within international society, the game of go uses black and white stones as an international language and that it is an ideal intellectual sport in which differences of nationality, sex, and age irrelevant. Based on this standpoint, the goal of the Pair Go tournament is not only to demonstrate the fascination of go as widely as possible by adopting the male-female pair system but also to develop this pair system as a new way of enjoying the game and to provide opportunities for international exchange on a regular, permanent and ever-increasing basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 21th Women&#39;s Go National Championship - Women&#39;s Championship</title>
      <link>http://redclould.github.io/posts/21women/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://redclould.github.io/posts/21women/</guid>
      <description>Official Website    http://www.haifong.org/?p=31188
Introduction    The 21th Women&amp;rsquo;s Go National Championship was held for over 20 years. It encouraged women to play Go and enjoy it. We believed that several players have been so much love in playing Go and attracting more people to join in this interesting field. Therefore, we hold this tournament just for female players to give them a showcase to show their abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 15th World Students GO OZA Championship – Women&#39;s Championship</title>
      <link>http://redclould.github.io/posts/15oza/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://redclould.github.io/posts/15oza/</guid>
      <description>Official Website    http://igooza.nikkei.co.jp/students/15th/index-we.htm  Introduction    The World Students GO OZA Championship is a championship in which 16 students chosen from various countries around the world, including from Asia, compete. It was founded in 2003, and the 15th championship will be held in February 2017. Not only the players but also the organizers are students: it&amp;rsquo;s an international championship run by students for students.
Championship outline     Name: The 15th World Students GO OZA Championship Organizer: The All-Japan Students GO Association / Nikkei Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 25th International Amateur Pair Go Championship - Runner-up</title>
      <link>http://redclould.github.io/posts/25pairgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://redclould.github.io/posts/25pairgo/</guid>
      <description>Official Website    http://www.pairgo.or.jp/amateur/25th/index_e.htm
Introduction    The 25th International Amateur Pair Go Championship were hold in Tokyo, from 8 to 9 December 2019. We believe that within international society, the game of go uses black and white stones as an international language and that it is an ideal intellectual sport in which differences of nationality, sex, and age irrelevant. Based on this standpoint, the goal of the Pair Go tournament is not only to demonstrate the fascination of go as widely as possible by adopting the male-female pair system but also to develop this pair system as a new way of enjoying the game and to provide opportunities for international exchange on a regular, permanent and ever-increasing basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd World Mind Sports Games – Women’s Individual Go Championship</title>
      <link>http://redclould.github.io/posts/wmsg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://redclould.github.io/posts/wmsg/</guid>
      <description>Official Website &amp;amp; References     [Official Website] http://www.imsaworld.com/wp/events-calendar/world-mind-sports-games-2012/ [Wikipedia] https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2012_World_Mind_Sports_Games   Introduction    The 2012 World Mind Sports Games were held in Lille, France, from 9 to 23 August 2012. The meet started during the 2012 Summer Olympics and ending shortly before the 2012 Summer Paralympics, both in London. This was the second rendition of the World Mind Sports Games, inaugurated 2008 in Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
